Marco Antonio V Montoya



Montreal, Canada



(514) 209-5032



marcovmontoya.xyz



MarcoVMontoya1989



marcovmontoya@gmail.com

PROFILE

Professional developer with 5 years of experience in web development, specialized in ReactJS, JavaScript frameworks. Always combining my passion for programming & technology I'm a self-driven person, committed to achieving results, with keen eye for details, looking for the best solution to problems with best code practices.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer FrontEnd, Mexico City

June 2017 - April 2019 LINIO REGIONAL LATAM

Working in FrontEnd and BackEnd team in charge to create new features to improve, integrate the content and new features of the website, debugging and improving the UI experience, improving API for mobile team,

creating new features to have impact on purchaces, reviewing code form other developers, unit test, also I worked for other clients to maintain Hewlett Packard, Banco Pacifico (Ecuador), Club Premier, Avianca Lifemiles using the Linio template.

Windows Azure Consultant & Developer, Mexico City

October 2015 - November 2016 CLOUD CONTINUITY SYSTEMS SERVICES

Responsible of developing web pages (mainly web design with C# and ASP.NET) to implement the Cloud Services using Azure Websites Services API.

Intern Consultant & Software Developer, Mexico City

August 2014 – February 2015 CLOUD CONTINUITY SYSTEMS SERVICES

Responsible in the participation of CSP projects with Azure in the creation of demos from Azure Portal.

EDUCATION

AEC Web Design and Programming - CDI College Montreal

August 2019 – February 2021 AEC COLLEGE DEGREE

Project Management Specialization - Panamerican University Mexico

August 2014 - July 2015 BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING SPECIALIZAITION

Information Technology and Intelligent Systems Engineer - Panamerican University Mexico

August 2009 - July 2014 BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

SKILLS

JavaScript	Redux	NodeJS	Git	Photoshop
React	MySQL	Express	CSS	Illustrator
TDD	MongoDB	Bootstrap	SASS	Blender
OOP	Mongoose	ThreeIS	HTML5	

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - Professional Proficiency

OTHER

Hearing Loss - Use of Cochlear implant.

HOBBY

VideoGames, Blender, Books, Board Game.